<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>graphql on Brighton Kotlin</title>
    <link>/tags/graphql/</link>
    <description>Recent content in graphql on Brighton Kotlin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2021 Brighton Kotlin | &lt;a href=&#34;/code-of-conduct/&#34;&gt;Code of Conduct&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 17:09:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/graphql/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Using GraphQL in a KMM project with Jetpack Compose and SwiftUI with John O&#39;Reilly</title>
      <link>/blog/using-graphqpl-kmm-project-with-jetpack-compose-and-swiftui-john-oreilly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 17:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/using-graphqpl-kmm-project-with-jetpack-compose-and-swiftui-john-oreilly/</guid>
      <description>In this talk John will show how GraphQL, using Apollo library, can be used in shared code a Kotlin Multiplatform project that uses Jetpack Compose Android and SwiftUI iOS clients.
The talk will cover:
use of Apollo GraphQL library, and it&amp;rsquo;s Kotlin Multiplatform support allowing addition of GraphQL queries and related logic in code shared between iOS and Android clients. development of clients using Declarative UI frameworks (using Jetpack Compose on Android and SwiftUI on iOS) Bio John O&amp;rsquo;Reilly is a Software Engineer at Neat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling UI across platforms with Server Driven UI by Joe Birch</title>
      <link>/blog/scaling-ui-across-platforms-server-driven-ui-joe-birch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 18:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/scaling-ui-across-platforms-server-driven-ui-joe-birch/</guid>
      <description>Mobile, Web, Desktop&amp;hellip; when working with multiple platforms for your product, you might start to feel like there is a lot for your team to maintain. If we update the design for a feature or want to test a new layout, we often need to make that change in multiple clients. This results in more time spent on the same task in multiple places, with less time being able to focus on delivering even more value to your users.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
