<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brighton Kotlin</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Brighton Kotlin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2021 Brighton Kotlin</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 22:09:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Xmas Drinks</title>
      <link>/blog/2019-xmas-drinks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 22:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019-xmas-drinks/</guid>
      <description>Even though it is short notice, we thought what better way to finish the year than gathering in a pub and having a few drinks to celebrate a great end to the year.
It would be great to see at the Hope and Ruin on the 16th December from 6:30pm on-wards
We already have some great speakers lined up for the beginning of 2020 and we will be publishing those events very soon but for now, join us to toast the end of the year in Brighton Kotlin style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I learnt from a major sports brand app by Kübra Harmankaya</title>
      <link>/blog/what-i-learnt-from-a-major-sports-brand-app-by-kubra-harmankaya/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 22:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/what-i-learnt-from-a-major-sports-brand-app-by-kubra-harmankaya/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our November Brighton Kotlin featuring Kübra Harmankaya as our guest speaker!
If you are new to Kotlin or interested in Kotlin on mobile, this is a great meetup for you. Kubra will share her experiences why we should convert Android applications into modern Kotlin, how to start converting a Java project and best Kotlin practices.
Kübra has contributed to Android apps for FC Barcelona, Premier League, British Council and for many other companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kotlin Multiplatform at HMRC By George Herbert</title>
      <link>/blog/kolin-multiplatform-hmrc-george-herbert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 22:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/kolin-multiplatform-hmrc-george-herbert/</guid>
      <description>We are extremely lucky to have a talk this month by George Herbert from Capgemini where he will discuss how Kotlin Multiplatform (KMP) was implemented at HMRC.
During this talk, he will talk about the reasons behind the use of KMP and how he made it work with iOS, Android and Web. Come along to find out whether KMP could be used in your projects or maybe just to pique your interest into the world of KMP!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Successful Inaugural Brighton Kotlin Meetup</title>
      <link>/blog/successful-inaugural-brighton-kotlin-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2019 22:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/successful-inaugural-brighton-kotlin-meetup/</guid>
      <description>It was great to see so many people come along to the first ever Brighton Kotlin meetup. It really showed that there is an active Kotlin community in Brighton with people working on projects using a range of technologies from the Kotlin ecosystem. You can see the photos of the event at our meetup page - https://www.meetup.com/Brighton-Kotlin/photos/30344969/
At this meetup Lee Turner talked about how Crunch have been introducing Kotlin into their backend microservice architecture over the past year, the results and challenges they have seen during that time and where they plan to take it next.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kotlin/Everywhere - Inaugural Brighton Kotlin Meetup</title>
      <link>/blog/kotlin-everywhere-inaugural-brighton-kotlin-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 22:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/kotlin-everywhere-inaugural-brighton-kotlin-meetup/</guid>
      <description>This will be the inaugural Brighton Kotlin meetup. The talks on the night are yet to be announced.
The meetup is hosted and sponsored by Crunch who are providing pizza and a choice of alcoholic and non-alcoholic drinks.
RSVPs close at 5pm on the day, with Doors at 6:30pm. Talks will begin at 7:15pm.
Sign up on our meetup page - https://www.meetup.com/Brighton-Kotlin/events/264170536/
This meetup is also supported by JetBrains who have provided us with a 1-year subscription to any of their IDEs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Brighton Kotlin meetup group. This group is for Kotlin users, enthusiasts and learners from beginners to experts, and anyone wanting to get involved with the Kotlin/JVM ecosystem.
We plan to have regular meetups, presentations and talks, and are always interested in hearing what people want to know about, so please let us know.
Visit our Meetup Page and sign up to come along to our next event or follow us on Twitter for all the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Event Code of Conduct &amp;amp; Anti-Harrassment Policy The Google Developer Groups, Kotlin User Groups and other Community Groups organizing these events [&amp;ldquo;Organizers&amp;rdquo;] are dedicated to providing a harassment-free and inclusive event experience for everyone regardless of gender identity and expression, sexual orientation, disabilities, neurodiversity, physical appearance, body size, ethnicity, nationality, race, age, religion, or other protected category. They do not tolerate harassment of event participants in any form. The Organizers take violations of this policy seriously and will respond appropriately.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
