<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SpringBoot on Brighton Kotlin</title>
    <link>/tags/springboot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SpringBoot on Brighton Kotlin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2021 Brighton Kotlin | &lt;a href=&#34;/code-of-conduct/&#34;&gt;Code of Conduct&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 17:09:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/springboot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Validation in Kotlin using Konform with Andrew Liles &amp; Szaby Gyurko</title>
      <link>/blog/validation-in-kotlin-using-konform/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 17:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/validation-in-kotlin-using-konform/</guid>
      <description>In the first of our February 2022 talks will be welcoming Andrew Liles &amp;amp; Szaby Gyurko, the CTO and Head of Engineering at Reset Health. They will be talking about their experience of Validation in Kotlin using Konform.
Want a means to validate input in Kotlin using a Kotlin idiomatic syntax? Andrew &amp;amp; Szaby&amp;rsquo;s team is building server-side Kotlin REST applications and chose Spring as the framework but decided to look beyond the traditional simple Spring annotation-driven approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bootiful Kotlin with Josh Long</title>
      <link>/blog/bootiful-kotlin-josh-long/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 17:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/bootiful-kotlin-josh-long/</guid>
      <description>Spring Boot, the convention-over-configuration centric framework from the Spring team at Pivotal, marries Spring&amp;rsquo;s flexibility with conventional, common sense defaults to make application development on the JVM not just fly, but pleasant! Spring Boot aims to make address the common functional and non-functional requirements that gate quickly moving to production. The framework is as clean as it gets, wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be nice if the language matched its elegance?
Kotlin, the productivity-focused language from our friends at JetBrains, takes up the slack to make the experience leaner, cleaner and even more pleasant!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
