<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>arrow on Brighton Kotlin</title>
    <link>/tags/arrow/</link>
    <description>Recent content in arrow on Brighton Kotlin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2021 Brighton Kotlin | &lt;a href=&#34;/code-of-conduct/&#34;&gt;Code of Conduct&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:09:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/arrow/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Best of Both Worlds - Kotlin &#43; FP with Shelby Cohen and Katie Levy</title>
      <link>/blog/the-best-of-both-worlds-kotlin-fp-shelby-cohen-katie-levy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/the-best-of-both-worlds-kotlin-fp-shelby-cohen-katie-levy/</guid>
      <description>Functional Programming is an excellent way to simplify your code and reduce bugs, and to make things even better, Kotlin provides a natural transition to using Functional Programming paradigms. But before that, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about what Functional Programming even is. In this talk, we&amp;rsquo;ll break down the key aspects of what defines Functional Programming and the key benefits of using Functional Programming paradigms. Then we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through how to use Functional Programming more in your Kotlin code to really have the best of both worlds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Functional Kotlin with Arrow by Karin-Aleksandra Monoid</title>
      <link>/blog/functional-kotlin-with-arrow-karin-aleksandra-monoid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 18:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/functional-kotlin-with-arrow-karin-aleksandra-monoid/</guid>
      <description>The July Brighton Kotlin meetup takes place on Thursday 22nd July at 6 pm GMT. We will be opening the zoom just before 6pm for people to gather and chat.
We&amp;rsquo;ll be welcoming Karin-Aleksandra Monoid who will be talking about Functional Kotlin with Arrow:
What is a monad? Do I need a PhD to write in functional style? How do I do that in Kotlin? And other questions that you were afraid to ask.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
