<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kotlin on Brighton Kotlin</title>
    <link>/tags/kotlin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kotlin on Brighton Kotlin</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2021 Brighton Kotlin | &lt;a href=&#34;/code-of-conduct/&#34;&gt;Code of Conduct&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 18:07:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/kotlin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>KotlinConf Global 2024 - Brighton Kotlin</title>
      <link>/blog/kotlin-global-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 18:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/kotlin-global-2024/</guid>
      <description>Details&#xA;This year Brighton Kotlin is taking part in KotlinConf Global 2024, where communities around the world are encouraged to become part of KotlinConf 2024 by hosting their own events. Join us on the 28th May for an engaging and informative KotlinConf Global at Runway East, Brighton.&#xA;This is a unique opportunity for Kotlin enthusiasts and professionals to come together, watch keynote talks from KotlinConf &amp;lsquo;24 in Copenhagen, and chat about the latest news from the Kotlin ecosystem, all over a few drinks and some pizza</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Source to Rule Them All - DSLs as a Single Source of Truth for Multiple Tasks with Ivan Ponomarev</title>
      <link>/blog/dsls-as-a-single-source-truth-ivan-ponomarev/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 17:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/dsls-as-a-single-source-truth-ivan-ponomarev/</guid>
      <description>We are very excited to welcome Ivan Ponomarev as the first Brighton Kotlin speaker of 2024. Ivan is a Staff Software Engineer at Synthesized and will be giving a talk on - One Source to Rule Them All: Kotlin DSLs as a Single Source of Truth for Multiple Tasks&#xA;In this talk, I will discuss how the DSL feature in the Kotlin language aids in building better products. We&amp;rsquo;ll explore the motivation for using DSLs, differentiating between external and internal DSLs, and delve into the advantages and limitations of internal Kotlin DSLs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kotlin - a bit of history with Andrey Breslav</title>
      <link>/blog/kotlin-a-bit-of-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 21:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/kotlin-a-bit-of-history/</guid>
      <description>Come and join us by signing up on our meetup page: https://www.meetup.com/brighton-kotlin/events/296107142/&#xA;We are very excited to welcome Andrey Breslav to our November meetup. Andrey is the Co-founder of Alter and was the Lead Language Designer for Kotlin at JetBrains. He will be giving a talk on Kotlin: a bit of history&#xA;This talk will give an overview of how Kotlin was developed and how it progressed looking from the inside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Kotlin Type Aliases To Automate Microservice Integration</title>
      <link>/blog/type-aliases-automate-microservice-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 10:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/type-aliases-automate-microservice-integration/</guid>
      <description>We are very excited to welcome Marty Pitt from Orbital. He will be giving a talk on Using Kotlin Type Aliases To Automate Microservice Integration&#xA;As teams embrace microservices, and the number of APIs, Topics and DBs explode, integration can become time-consuming to build, and a maintenance nightmare.&#xA;This talk explores using semantic metadata (powered by Kotlin type aliases) to automate integration between all your APIs, Message queues, serverless functions and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with the Micronaut Framework</title>
      <link>/blog/getting-started-with-micronaut/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 10:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/getting-started-with-micronaut/</guid>
      <description>We are very excited to welcome Sergio del Amo Caballero. He will be giving a talk on Getting Started with the Micronaut Framework&#xA;In this session, Sergio del Amo introduces the Micronaut® framework and demonstrates how the Framework&amp;rsquo;s unique compile-time approach enables the development of ultra-lightweight Java applications.&#xA;Compelling aspects of the Micronaut framework include:&#xA;Develop applications with Java, Kotlin, or Apache Groovy Sub-second startup time Small processes that can run in as little as 10 MB of JVM heap No runtime reflection Dependency injection and AOP Reflection-free serialization A database access toolkit that uses ahead-of-time (AoT) compilation to pre-compute queries for repository interfaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Architecture Design with Koin with Arnaud Giuliani</title>
      <link>/blog/android-architecture-design-with-koin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 10:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/android-architecture-design-with-koin/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ll be welcoming Arnaud Giuliani so sign up, spread the word, BYOB and pizza, and join the conversation!&#xA;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash; Arnaud Giuliani &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash; Android Architecture Design with Koin&#xA;Koin (https://insert-koin.io) is a pragmatic dependency injection framework for Kotlin/Android developers, well known for its ease of use.&#xA;In this session, I propose to see together how we can structure our components, for the following topics:&#xA;Classical Components in MVP, MVVM Dealing with Scopes Jetpack Navigation Jetpack Compose Integrating with Multi-Platform And an overview of incoming new features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Successful Inaugural Brighton Kotlin Meetup</title>
      <link>/blog/successful-inaugural-brighton-kotlin-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2019 22:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/successful-inaugural-brighton-kotlin-meetup/</guid>
      <description>It was great to see so many people come along to the first ever Brighton Kotlin meetup. It really showed that there is an active Kotlin community in Brighton with people working on projects using a range of technologies from the Kotlin ecosystem. You can see the photos of the event at our meetup page - https://www.meetup.com/Brighton-Kotlin/photos/30344969/&#xA;At this meetup Lee Turner talked about how Crunch have been introducing Kotlin into their backend microservice architecture over the past year, the results and challenges they have seen during that time and where they plan to take it next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kotlin/Everywhere - Inaugural Brighton Kotlin Meetup</title>
      <link>/blog/kotlin-everywhere-inaugural-brighton-kotlin-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 22:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/kotlin-everywhere-inaugural-brighton-kotlin-meetup/</guid>
      <description>This will be the inaugural Brighton Kotlin meetup. The talks on the night are yet to be announced.&#xA;The meetup is hosted and sponsored by Crunch who are providing pizza and a choice of alcoholic and non-alcoholic drinks.&#xA;RSVPs close at 5pm on the day, with Doors at 6:30pm. Talks will begin at 7:15pm.&#xA;Sign up on our meetup page - https://www.meetup.com/Brighton-Kotlin/events/264170536/&#xA;This meetup is also supported by JetBrains who have provided us with a 1-year subscription to any of their IDEs.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
