<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kotlin on Brighton Kotlin</title>
    <link>/tags/kotlin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kotlin on Brighton Kotlin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2021 Brighton Kotlin | &lt;a href=&#34;/code-of-conduct/&#34;&gt;Code of Conduct&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 10:09:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/kotlin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with the Micronaut Framework</title>
      <link>/blog/getting-started-with-micronaut/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 10:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/getting-started-with-micronaut/</guid>
      <description>We are very excited to welcome Sergio del Amo Caballero. He will be giving a talk on Getting Started with the Micronaut Framework
In this session, Sergio del Amo introduces the Micronaut® framework and demonstrates how the Framework&amp;rsquo;s unique compile-time approach enables the development of ultra-lightweight Java applications.
Compelling aspects of the Micronaut framework include:
Develop applications with Java, Kotlin, or Apache Groovy Sub-second startup time Small processes that can run in as little as 10 MB of JVM heap No runtime reflection Dependency injection and AOP Reflection-free serialization A database access toolkit that uses ahead-of-time (AoT) compilation to pre-compute queries for repository interfaces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Architecture Design with Koin with Arnaud Giuliani</title>
      <link>/blog/android-architecture-design-with-koin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 10:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/android-architecture-design-with-koin/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ll be welcoming Arnaud Giuliani so sign up, spread the word, BYOB and pizza, and join the conversation!
&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash; Arnaud Giuliani &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash; Android Architecture Design with Koin
Koin (https://insert-koin.io) is a pragmatic dependency injection framework for Kotlin/Android developers, well known for its ease of use.
In this session, I propose to see together how we can structure our components, for the following topics:
Classical Components in MVP, MVVM Dealing with Scopes Jetpack Navigation Jetpack Compose Integrating with Multi-Platform And an overview of incoming new features.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
